Ayanna Pressley, Jamal Bowman, they were the last people that I decided that I'm going to
way forward. We want to continue to piecemeal everything and go about it, individual, organization.
Their value systems are meant to serve money. Conversations to really get to the bottom of
where do we go from here? And that's really what I wanted to hear. You know, people talking about
like, well, these are the ways that we can come together to support policy change. When you get
elected in office, they have you do a five, we need a five-year strategic plan. This will help
people really want to just do their due diligence and really understand locally. Amanda, no, this is
not good. Why are you taking your hair out on a live? Some things are personal and we don't need
to see that. It seems as if you're unraveling emotionally. This is how elders get disrespected.
Statements like this. Ma'am, do not displace your insecurities onto me.
What you don't need to see is me taking out a tampon, okay? What you don't need to see is me
getting a colonoscopy, okay? Me taking out fake hair from my real hair on a live as I communicate
with the community on ways in which we can advance our community is the definition of emotionally
together. Furthermore, it is demonstrative of me being wholly aware of my role in my community
and of my ability to multitask. So really what you should be doing is taking lessons because
what you're witnessing is a sister who knows herself and who is sure of herself and who knows
that the visual representation of herself in a less than together state is actually a demonstration
of how together she is. Out her goddamn mind. Out of her goddamn mind.
Who are the limitations y'all put on yourselves? I thank God every day how free I am in here.